buddyhead.com 2010-05-16

# PRIVACY | BUDDYHEAD

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

Buddyhead II, LLC (“Buddyhead”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Buddyhead managed domains (currently Buddyhead.com) and websites or domain name, or any other linked pages, features, content, or application services offered from time to time by Buddyhead in connection therewith (collectively, the “Website”), submitting information, or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?**

This Privacy Policy covers Buddyhead’s treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that Buddyhead gathers when you are accessing Buddyhead’s Website and when you use Buddyhead services. Also, this Privacy Policy covers Buddyhead’s treatment of any Personal Information that Buddyhead’s business partners share with Buddyhead. This policy does not apply to the practices third parties that Buddyhead does not own or control, or to individuals that Buddyhead does not employ or manage.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES BUDDYHEAD COLLECT?**  
The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services and to allow our users to set up a user account and profile that can be used to interact with other users through the Website. In connection with the Website, we request and display some personal information to other users and visitors of Website, which allows users to identify each other. We collect the following types of information from our customers.

**Personal Information You Provide to Us:**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our Website or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected include, without limitation, your full name, email address, IP address, browser information, password, contact information, sms information, credit card or bank account information, transactional information based on your activities on the Website, and media consumed on the Website including, but not limited to, media viewed, played, downloaded, uploaded, and shared. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide is used for purposes such as responding to your requests for certain products and services, allowing you to interact with other users, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about specials, sales offers, and new features.

**Personal Information Collected Automatically:**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Website or services. Buddyhead automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Buddyhead cookie information, the page you requested, and the media you have consumed (e.g., viewed, played, downloaded, uploaded, and shared).  
Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. This type of data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Website or services so that we can make the Website appealing to as many customers as possible, and improve those services. As part of this use of information, (i) we may provide information to the content owners that relates to their fans (e.g., regarding which fans are consuming and sharing what pieces of media at what levels), and (ii) we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our site (e.g., we share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and our Website, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience).

**Communications:**  
Buddyhead is a retailer of Buddyhead Record’s artists and third party artists music, video and multimedia content.  Buddyhead markets media directly to users of the site through e-mails, sms, phone/voicemail and other forms of communication. We often receive a confirmation when you access a message from your Buddyhead or other device. Buddyhead uses this confirmation to improve the effectiveness of the marketing. If you do not want to receive such communication from us, please choose the appropriate setting in the account management area of the Website to not receive correspondence from the Buddyhead directly or from the Buddyhead on behalf of the artist.

**What About Cookies?**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Buddyhead cookies do not collect Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is.  
Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Website’s most attractive features.  
Ads and offers appearing on the Website may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Buddyhead and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Buddyhead does not access or control such third party cookies; please refer to those Companies’ privacy policies.

**WILL BUDDYHEAD SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?**  
Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to other people or nonaffiliated companies. We may share your Personal Information when we have your permission, and we may share Your Personal Information under the following circumstances:

Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: We are affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses sell items to you through Buddyhead’s Website, for example, the bands, musicians and other artists from which you purchase or use products or services through the Website. In other situations, Buddyhead provides services, or sells products jointly with affiliated businesses. Usually, you will be able to easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction. We will share Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business.

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples of such information include, without limitation, fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, analyzing data, processing credit card information and providing customer service. Unless we tell you differently, Buddyhead’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

User Profiles: User profile information including users’ name, email address, contact information, and other information you enter (“User Submissions”) may be displayed to artists to facilitate direct communication with artists and users. Email addresses are used to add new User Submissions to user profiles and to communicate through User Submissions. Do not disclose your password to anyone. If you share your password or your Personal Information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lost control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your Personal Information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if you password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Buddyhead and change your password.

Business Transfers: If Buddyhead, or substantially all of its business or assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Buddyhead goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by the successor or acquirer (or a third party through bankruptcy). You acknowledge that such transfers may occur in any of these circumstances, and that any acquiror or successor of Buddyhead may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.  
Protection of Buddyhead and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Buddyhead, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  
With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

**IS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?**  
Your Buddyhead account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to ensure unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.  
Buddyhead endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private; however, Buddyhead cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.  
The Website contains links to other sites, including the sites of the bands, musicians and other artists from which you purchase or use products or services through the Website. Buddyhead is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites (including the bands, musicians and other artists from which you purchase or use products or services through the Website). When linking to another site you should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Website.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?**  
Buddyhead allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list will change as our Website changes.  
Contact information  
Billing information  
E-mail subscriptions to artists  
Paid subscriptions to artists  
Transaction history  
Media consumption history

**WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?**  
As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information to use, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain Buddyhead features.  
You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “What Personal Information Can I Access” section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.  
You may request deletion of your Buddyhead account by sending an e-mail to customersupport@Buddyhead.com. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.  
If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please log in to the Website and select the appropriate setting in the Account Management area of the Website. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Buddyhead Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
Buddyhead may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted.

**QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at Buddyhead site, please send us a detailed message to customersupport@buddyhead.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.  
Effective Date: March 2009  
Buddyhead II, LLC  
P.O. Box 1267  
Hollywood, CA 90078  
customersupport@buddyhead.com

Popularity: unranked
